Kevin Miller

Culver City, CA 90230 klmille@gmail.com (310) 562-4572

I have experience in clerical work, as well as experience in supervising the daily management of a business. My education taught me to be a good problem-solver and multi-tasker. I am also friendly and interact well with customers and team members alike. Outside of work, I regularly meet up with people in a dance instruction setting, and I enjoy playing and dancing to music.

Work Experience

Property Manager and Accountant

Twinwood, Inc October 2013 to Present

Daily manager of a small business, involved in accounting and property repair service.

Lab Technician

Praxair

October 2014 to February 2015

Analytical scientist involved in maintaining rigorous safety standards in a laboratory setting while achieving high analytical throughput.

Researcher / Teaching Assistant

University of California - Los Angeles, CA September 2007 to July 2013

- Supervisor of multiple undergraduate chemistry labs
- Teacher for various chemistry discussion courses at the college level
- Mentor to individual undergraduates in a research lab
- · Collaborator on scientific research with other groups and universities for several publications
- Author of seven research papers published in well-regarded scientific journals

Researcher

University of California - Irvine, CA August 2006 to June 2007

Wrote, budgeted, and helped follow through on a scientific research proposal.

Associate Inventory Manager

ChromaDex, Inc - Irvine, CA June 2006 to June 2007

Organizer and handler of a large chemical database of botanical reference standards.

Education

Ph.D. in Chemistry

University of California - Los Angeles, CA December 2014

B. S. in Chemistry

University of California - Irvine, CA June 2007

Skills

- EXCEL (10+ years)
- MICROSOFT WORD (10+ years)
- POWERPOINT (10+ years)
- QUICKBOOKS (4 years)

Awards

Dissertation Year Fellowship Award

September 2011

Chemistry research fellowship

Ralph and Charlene Bauer Award for Research in Inorganic Chemistry

September 2010

Undergraduate Research Opportunities Program Fellow

January 2007

Chemistry research fellowship

OULA Training Scholarship

September 2017

Scholarship for dance instructor certification

Certifications and Licenses

CPR / AED, Pediatric CPR, and First Aid

October 2017 to October 2018

Publications

Dearomatization reactions of N-heterocycles mediated by group III complexes $2010\,$

Reactions of aromatic N-heterocycles with a lutetium benzyl complex supported by a ferrocene-diamide ligand

2010

Reactions of imidazoles with electrophilic metal alkyl complexes $2010\,$

Group 3 metal complexes of radical-anionic 2,2'-bipyridyl ligands 2010

Reactions of group III biheterocyclic complexes

2011

An unusual hydrogen migration/C-H activation reaction with group 3 metals 2011

Synthesis of symmetrically and unsymmetrically 3,5-dimethylbenzylsubstituted 1,1'-ferrocene diamines

2011

Additional Information

Dance

- Volunteer at Santa Monica Family YMCA
- Dance Instructor certification pending for OULA dance
- Certified in CPR / AED, Pediatric CPR, and First Aid by the American Red Cross
- Participant in various weekly dance and fitness classes

Bands

- Bassist and singer for The Psychic Ferns, for which I helped compose, record, and release original music thepsychicferns.bandcamp.com
- Bassist for The Coop Band a small cover band